

Web Developer specializing in front end development.

I am a persistent, committed, self-motivated and a very professional individual. I have always carried out all the tasks assigned to me without hesitation. On the other hand, I am a creative person and I love to test my boundaries. In order to do so, I keep pushing myself to think out of the box!

AJINKYA SAMPATRAO SHEWALE

Phone:

+91 909 623 7473

E-Mail:

ajinkyashewale29@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/AjinkyaSampatra oShewale

VisitMe@:

https://ajinkyashewale.github.io/

Objective

Looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical, database, management skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector.

Skill Highlights

Angular 4-8	*	*	*	*	*	*	
TypeScript	*	*	*	*			
JavaScript	*	*	*	*			
HTML5	*	*	*	*	*	*	
CSS3	*	*	*	*	*	*	
SCSS	*	*	*	*	*	*	
Bootstrap	*	*	*	*	*	*	
jQuery	*	*	*	*	*		
SQL	*	*	*	*			
Git	*	*	*	*			

Interest

Family and Friends Code new things Internet Surfing

Education

Master of Engineering: Computer Science and Engineering - @ADCET, Ashta, Shivaji University with 63.13

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Science and Engineering - @SBGI, Miraj, Shivaji University with 63.87

HSC: @DPKM, Sangli, Kolhapur Divisional Board with 55.33

SSC: @HHRCPH, Sangli, Kolhapur Divisional Board with 66.61

Professional Experience

06/2019 to present

Software Developer - MeLayer Software Solutions PVT. LTD., Pune as per consultancy services

- Working as a web developer as per consultancy services.
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites

04/2017 to present

Assistant Professor - ATS'S, SBGI, MIRAJ

- Taught Web Technology for 4 years.
- Technical Event Head.
- E-Grievance Head and so on Active in all events

01/2016 to 03/2017

Software Developer - MeLayer Software Solutions PVT. LTD., Pune

- Working as a full-time web developer
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

Hands-on Experience

1.	Project Title	Dealer Management System (DMS)			
	Platform	Angular 8, Bootstrap 4, CSS3, SCSS, HTML5, Java SpringBoot, MYSQL.			
	Duration	January 2020 to till			
	Description	In this project we implemented a micro front-end concept. This project			
	-	is divided into 5 sub modules i.e. sales-presales, spare-part, warranty,			
		services, master. These 5 modules load into one main module.			
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in requirement gathering and documentation.			
	·	✓ Involved in coding, development.			
		✓ Team Member of UI/UX and Development of a front end.			
2.	Project Title	Customer Relationship Management (CRM)			
	Platform	Angular 8, Bootstrap 4, CSS3, SCSS, HTML5, Java SpringBoot, MYSQL.			
	Duration	December 2019 to February 2020			
	Description	The main focus of the project is service call management and service			
	•	tracking. Application is divided into 3 parts i.e. Service Tracking is a			
		Mobile based and web-based application, Complaint tracking and			
		Technician Tracking.			
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in requirement gathering and documentation.			
	·	✓ Involved in coding, development.			
		✓ Team Member of UI/UX and Development of a front end.			
3.	Project Title	Dynamic Web Application with Content Management System (CMS)			
	Platform	Angular 5, Bootstrap 4, HTML5, ng-Bootstrap, CSS3, SCSS, Angular			
		Material.			
	Duration	June 2019 to November 2019			
	Description	This is an event and club management project in this project: create an			
		event and manage event related activities like creating an event,			
		update event, event advertising show popular club and event in			
		particular city and membership.			
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in requirement gathering and documentation.			
		✓ Involved in coding, development.			
		✓ Team Member of UI/UX and Development of a front end.			
		✓ Firebase, Firebase Auth.			
4.	Project Title	Shree Shaineshwar Railway Services			
	Platform	Bootstrap 4, CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery.			
	Duration	November 2018			
	Description	This project mainly focuses on a static information share route map			
		and contact information of shree shaineshwar organization.			
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in requirement gathering and documentation.			
		✓ Involved in coding, development.			
		✓ UI/UX and Development of a front end.			
5.	Project Title	Moodle Exam Server			
	Platform	Bootstrap 4, CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL.			
	Duration	February 2017			
	Description	Moodle exam server is for conducting exam in a LAN or online with			
		calculation of rank and accepting feedback from attendee. Also storing			
		registration information of exam attendee.			
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in requirement gathering and documentation.			
	·	✓ Involved in coding, development.			
		✓ UI/UX and Development of a front end also database connectivity.			
		1 Signature Development of a front end also database connectivity.			

6.	Project Title	Online Feedback Server				
	Platform	Bootstrap 4, CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL.				
	Duration	April 2016				
	Description	Online feedback server is implemented for ATS'S SBGI engineering				
		college feedback is accepting from students and generate the printable				
		feedbacks according to class-wise and subject-wise also department-				
		wise.				
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in requirement gathering and documentation.				
		✓ Involved in coding, development.				
		✓ UI/UX and Development of a front end also database connectivity.				
7.	Project Title	My Personal Web Platform				
	Platform	Bootstrap 4, CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP.				
	Duration	April 2016				
	Description	For self-promotion I have developed my personal web platform which				
		defines me and for this I have referred template from the internet and				
		had modified it.				
	Role & Responsibilities	✓ Involved in coding, development.				
		✓ UI/UX and Development of a front end.				

Achievements

Oracle Certification in Java Programming (OCJP).



Microsoft Technology Associate in Database Administrations Fundamentals.



Microsoft Certified Professional.



Publications

1. A. A. Gidd, S. A. Molaj and A. S. Shewale, "Role of Artificial Intelligence in Medical Science," 2019 Third International conference on I-SMAC (IoT in Social, Mobile, Analytics and Cloud) (I-SMAC), Palladam, India, 2019, pp. 556-560. doi: 10.1109/I-SMAC47947.2019.9032586 keywords: {artificial intelligence;decision making;medical computing;artificial intelligence;medical science;medical field;decision making;Conferences;Artificial Intelligence;Medical Science;Diagnosis;Robots;Deep Learning},

URL: http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?tp=&arnumber=9032586&isnumber=9032424

2. Ajinkya S. Shewale and Sandeep G. Sutar, "Enhanced Identity Management and Security in IoT backing with Cloud using ICAC," ICICA 2016 International Conference on Intelligent Computing and Applications and 3rd international conference on Po, Circuit and Information Technologies., pp. 501-510. keywords: {Access control; Internet of things; IPv4; IPv6; Smart cities.},

URL: http://www.serialsjournals.com/serialjournalmanager/pdf/1

Personal Profile

Full Name: Mr. Ajinkya Sampatrao Shewale

Date of Birth: 05/10/1991
Marital Status: Married

Permanent Address: SHREE, Lokseva Stationary, opposite Shantiniketan College, Sangli 416 416.

Current Address: Same as above

Languages Known: English, Marathi, Hindi.

Declaration

Place:

		Yours Sincerely,	
Date:			

Mr. Ajinkya Sampatrao Shewale

The above information is true as per best of my knowledge. I am waiting for a positive response at your

end. I will assure you positive results if I get the chance to serve in your Organization.